http://www.bgthamilton.com/index.php/privacy-policy

HomeMinistriesCOVID-19 UpdatesKidsKids VBS 2020SURGE Youth (Gr. 6-8)SURGE Youth (Gr. 9-12)Young AdultsWomen's MinistryMen's MinistrySeniors' MinistryBible StudyPrayerWorship / MusicBus MinistryPlan to ProtectSmall GroupsSportsAlphaMinistry to WidowsWe ShareGrief ShareDivorce CareAbout UsMission & VisionOur BeliefsMinistry TeamAdministrative StaffBoard of DeaconsMedia ZoneVideo MessagesRightNow MediaDaily Bible Reading PlanContact UsOnline GivingOther Ways to Give
Privacy Policy Statement
Bethel Gospel Tabernacle (Hamilton) Incorporated
Our Commitment
Bethel Gospel Tabernacle (BGT) is committed to protecting the privacy of the personal information of its employees, members, and donors. We value the trust of those with whom we deal, and of the public, and recognize that maintaining this trust requires that we be transparent and accountable in how we treat the information that we have in our files.
During the course of activities of our various ministries, we frequently gather and use personal information. Anyone from whom we collect such information should expect that it will be carefully protected. Our privacy practices are designed to achieve this. Protecting your privacy means:
We keep personal information in strict confidence
We do not rent, sell or trade our mailing lists.
You have control over how we obtain, use and give out information about you.
You have access to the information we have about you.
Defining Personal Information
Personal information is any information that can be used to distinguish, identify, or contact a specific individual.
Bethel Gospel Tabernacle (BGT) maintains name and address information to keep members and donors informed and up-to-date on the activities of the ministries of Bethel Gospel Tabernacle (BGT), including programs, services, donation opportunities and donation receipts. We also maintain information on prior years donations and donation receipt numbers as required by Canada Customs and Revenue Agency for receipt verification.
Privacy Practices
Personal information gathered by Bethel Gospel Tabernacle (BGT) is kept in confidence. Our personnel are authorized to access personal information based only on their need to deal with the information for the reason(s) for which it was obtained. Safeguards are in place to ensure that the information is not disclosed or shared more widely than is necessary to achieve the purpose for which it was gathered. We also take measures to ensure the integrity of this information is maintained and to prevent its being lost or destroyed. We collect, use and disclose personal information only for purposes that a reasonable person would consider appropriate in light of the circumstances.
Consent
Express consent can be verbal or written. Consent may be implied when we can reasonably conclude that you have given consent by some action you decide to take, or you decide not to take. For example, when you make a donation, it is implied that you are giving your written consent to retain information for the purposes of advising you regarding further donation opportunities and/or for receipting purposes. You can withdraw your consent any time after you have given it to us, provided there are no legal requirements to prevent this. Otherwise we keep your information only for as long as needed to fulfill the intended purpose, or for a reasonable time thereafter, or to meet any legal requirements. Your information is destroyed when it is no longer needed.
Updating of Privacy Policy
We regularly review our privacy practices for our various activities, and update our policy. Please check this Web site on an ongoing basis for information on our most up to date practices.
Privacy Policy for Members
Bethel Gospel Tabernacle (BGT) only collects personal information as required with the full knowledge and consent of its members. Bethel Gospel Tabernacle (BGT) only discloses personal information about members with their full knowledge and consent given in advance.
Web Site and Electronic Commerce
Bethel Gospel Tabernacle (BGT) collects personal information through its Web site for very specific reasons and we always identify the purposes. If you make a donation, for example, we ask for your name and mailing address in order to send you a receipt for income tax purposes. If you wish to make a purchase or register for an event, we require your credit card number to process the order. If you leave a comment and wish a response, we need your e-mail address. Rest assured that Bethel Gospel Tabernacle (BGT)  only collects and uses your personal information, including your e-mail address, as necessary to fulfill your request. We use password protocols and encryption software to protect personal and other information we receive when a product or service is requested and/or paid for online. Our software is routinely updated to maximize protection of such information.
Contact Information
Questions, concerns or complaints relating to the Bethel Gospel Tabernacle (BGT) privacy policy on the treatment of personal information should be e-mailed to: This email address is being protected from spambots. You need JavaScript enabled to view it.. Further information on privacy and your rights to your personal information may be found on the Web site of the Privacy Commissioner of Canada at www.privcom.gc.ca.
Contact Us
Bethel Gospel Tabernacle1355 Upper Wellington St.Hamilton, ONL9A 3S8
Phone: (905) 387-6530Fax: (905) 387-4566mail@bgthamilton.com
© 2017 Bethel Gospel Tabernacle, Hamilton Inc.
